神啊  我一直怀疑你的存在  你为何抛弃我
Why hast thou forsaken me, O deity whose existence I doubt?
拿着  往袋子里呼气
Here. Breathe into this bag.
出什么事了
What's going on?
被他们扒得光光的啊  莱纳德
They stole everything, Leonard!
一点不剩
Everything.
你是他室友吗
Are you the roommate?
对  莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德  怎么了
Yeah, Leonard Hofstadter. What happened?
你朋友报警说自己被盗了
Your friend here called 911 to report a robbery.
哦天呐  他们偷走了啥
Oh, my God, what did they get?
你该问他们没偷走啥
What didn't they get?
偷走了我的附魔武器
They got my enchanted weapons,
我的邪恶角斗士盔甲
my vicious gladiator armor,
我的纯净力量之杖
my wand of untainted power,
还有全部的金币
and all my gold!
你居然就因为
You called the police
有人黑掉了你的魔兽世界账号就报警了
because someone hacked your World of Warcraft account?
我还能怎么办
What choice did I have?
谢耳朵大侠  85级的血精灵
The mighty Sheldor, level 85 blood elf,
东部王国的英雄
hero of the Eastern kingdoms,
像烈日下的尸骸一样被扒光了
has been picked clean, like a carcass in the desert sun.
另外  联邦调查局挂了我的电话
Plus, the FBI hung up on me.
往袋子里呼吸
Into the bag.
他们还偷走了我的作战陆行鸟
They took my battle ostrich!
-哦不会吧  别偷格兰啊  -是啊
- Oh, no, not Glenn! - Yes!
格兰
Glenn!
我唯一深爱的鸟啊
The only bird I ever loved.
保重了各位
Good luck, fellas.
谢谢你  警官
Oh. Well, thank you, officer.
等一等
Wait a minute!
你难道就这么放任不管吗
You're not going to do anything?
库珀先生  我无能...
Mr. Cooper, there's nothing...
是库珀博士
Dr. Cooper.
不是开玩笑吧
Seriously?
他不是那种贩毒的博士
Not the kind with access to drugs.
好吧  库珀博士
Fine. Dr. Cooper.
我对你的损失深表遗憾
I'm sorry for your loss,
但帕萨迪纳警局
but the Pasadena Police Department
的管辖权并不在
doesn't have jurisdiction in...
潘多拉
Pandora.
你说的那是《阿凡达》
That's from Avatar
魔兽世界可是在艾泽拉斯啊
World of Warcraft takes place in Azeroth.
我的亲娘七舅老爷  你是怎么有资格配枪的
Goodness gracious, how are you allowed to carry a gun?
你起码能给我推荐一位被开除的警察吧
Can you at least refer me to a rogue ex-cop?
什么
What?
就是  那种因为拒绝墨守陈规
Wh-- you know, one who was drummed off the force
而被开除的警察
because he refused to play by the rules,
现在致力于
and now he hires himself out
用自己的残酷方式伸张正义
to impose his own brand of rough justice?
没有
No.
多谢了  警官
Thank you, officer.
全没了  全没了啊
It's all gone. All gone.
我真的很遗憾  谢尔顿
I'm really sorry, Sheldon.
这是个什么世道啊
What kind of world do we live in,
一个人可以随便抢走另一个人的作战陆行鸟
where a man would take another man's battle ostrich?
我不知道
I don't know.
这种野蛮行径必须
This act of aggression must be met
以牙还牙以血还血
with swift and cruel ferocity.
大声疾呼的时刻到了  让我们释放战争恶魔吧
It is time to cry havoc, and let slip the dogs of war.
我这就去
I'm on it.
你好  沃罗威茨夫人  霍华德在家吗
Hi, Mrs. Wolowitz. Is, is Howard there?
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
那只战争恶魔
That particular dog of war
会在洗完澡以后回你电话
will have to call you back after his bath.
我看看拉杰有没有练完普拉提
See if Raj is done with Pilates.
生活大爆炸
第四季第十九集
三千个小时
Three thousand hours.
点了三千个小时的鼠标啊
Three thousand hours clicking on that mouse,
就为了收集武器和金币
collecting weapons and gold.
差一点就全是浪费时间了
It's almost as if it was a huge waste of time.
不管是谁干的  他肯定早有准备
Whoever did this knew what they were doing.
他在15分钟内登入登出了
He got in and out of your account in under
你的账号  其间弄走了你的全部物品
15 minutes, transferred all your stuff,
而且还没留下一丝的电子指纹
and didn't leave a digital fingerprint.
噢
Oh!
即使饮尽全世界的黄春菊茶[能稳定情绪]
There isn't enough chamomile tea in the world
也不能平息我心中的怒火
to quell the rage in my heart.
等下  我在雷霆崖的桥下
Hold on. I'm talking to an orc
跟一位兽人聊天
under the bridge in Thunder Bluff
他说只要我们肯出钱  他能帮我们找到你的东西
who says if we pay him, he'll help us track down your things.
他可信吗
Can we trust him?
我觉得挺可信的  他似乎是
I should say so; he appears to be a member
尼日利亚的一位皇室成员
of the Nigerian royal family.
哇  有人在拍卖一个镶了宝石陆行鸟缰绳
Whoa! Somebody's auctioning off a jeweled ostrich bridle!
不是  格兰的缰绳是皮革的
No. Glenn's was leather.
他以前是只很平凡的陆行鸟
He was a simple ostrich.
现在也是  现在也是  我还没放弃希望
Is! Is, I haven't given up hope.
嗨
Hey.
嗨  佩妮  我们现在正忙着处理些麻烦事
Hey, Penny. We're kind of in the middle of a crisis, here.
我知道  伯纳黛特告诉我了
Oh, I know. Bernadette told me.
不好意思啊谢尔顿  我知道那个游戏对你来说意义非凡
Sorry, Sheldon. I know that game meant a lot to you.
神马  "那个游戏"
What-- "that game"?
很抱歉佩妮  涂鸦跳跃是个游戏
Excuse me, Penny, but Doodle Jump is a game.
愤怒的小鸟也是个游戏
Angry Birds is a game.
魔兽世界是一款
World of Warcraft is a
大规模  多玩家的在线角色扮演
massively multi-player online role-playing...
好吧  严格来讲  也算是游戏
all right, technically it's a game.
坏消息  那个尼日利亚王子可能是个骗子
Bad news, the Nigerian prince may be a fraud.
好吧  总而言之  我带了个
Okay, well, anyways, I brought you
昨天出炉的芝士蛋糕来安慰你
a day-old cheesecake to cheer you up!
对一个失去陆行鸟的人来说
Stale pastry is hollow succor
一个不新鲜的蛋糕顶毛用呀
to a man who is bereft of ostrich.
说"谢谢"就好了
Just say "thank you".
我刚才说的不就是这意思嘛
I thought I just did.
好吧  回见
All right. See you later.
你好
Oh! Hello.
你好呀
Oh, hi!
我只是来送个芝士蛋糕给谢尔顿
I was just dropping off a cheesecake to Sheldon.
他被抢劫了  丢了一堆虚拟世界里
He was robbed of a bunch of imaginary crap
才用得上的那些虚拟破烂儿
that's useful in a make-believe place.
我没听懂
I don't know what that means.
很可惜  我听得懂
Yeah, well, sadly, I do.
你们知道上周末普丽娅带莱纳德
Did you know last weekend Priya took Leonard
去海滩玩轮滑吗
rollerblading at the beach?
你们能相信吗
Can you believe that?
我觉得我应该说"那个臭婊子"
I feel like I'm supposed to say "that bitch",
但我又不太了解状况
but I don't have enough information.
我才是那个花了两年时间
I am the one who spent two years
努力说服他
trying to get him to even
去沙滩的那个人
go to the beach in the first place.
而且他超怕踩到医疗垃圾
And he was so phobic about stepping on medical waste,
怕到我得背着他下水
I had to carry him to the water.
我也带霍华德去过一次海滩
I took Howard to the beach once.
他差点像个吸血鬼一样着起火来
He almost burst into flames like a vampire.
我费了那么大劲把莱纳德改造成
So what's the thanks I get for turning Leonard
一个超级无敌好男友  可结果我得到了什么
into quality boyfriend material?
我在他女朋友面前还得处处谨小慎微
I have to tiptoe around his new girlfriend.
你该说那句话了
I think you're on.
那个臭婊子
That bitch!
雪糕上要不要加点咖啡利口酒
Want some coffee liqueur on your ice cream?
这就是我妈警告过我的那种
Ah, here's the alcohol and drug peer pressure
同辈人会教唆我喝酒和嗑药的情景
Mother warned me about.
我还以为永远不会有这么一天呢
I was starting to think it was never going to happen.
我要  谢谢
Yes, please.
你们真应该见识一下我最初认识的莱纳德
You guys should've seen Leonard when I first met him.
他都不敢跟人有眼神交流
There was no eye contact.
他不是抬头看天花板
He was either looking up at the ceiling,
就是低头看他的鞋
or down at his shoes.
我醉了
I'm drunk.
刚开始的几个月
You know, for the first couple of months,
每次我脱掉胸衣
whenever I would take off my bra,
他都会傻笑着说  天啊  我最胸的朋友
he would giggle and say, "Oh, boy, my breast friends"!
不知道我这么说你会不会好受点
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
但我以后再也不会理普丽娅了
I'm never speaking to Priya again.
不  别这样
No, don't do that.
咱也没理由欺负她呀
No reason to be mean to her.
这也许是醉话
This may be the alcohol talking...
但我觉得咱还真有理由欺负她
but I believe there is.
你有没有听说过京都大学的西田
Are you familiar with the recent study
和保坂最近做的一项
of Tanzanian chimpanzees by Nishida and Hosaka
关于坦桑尼亚黑猩猩的研究
out of Kyoto University?
没有  但我可以叫出所有卡戴珊姐妹的名字
No, but I can name all the Kardashians.
像咱们这种灵长类动物  天生就会
Primates, such as ourselves, have a natural instinct
排斥族群里不守规矩的成员
to ostracize ill-mannered members of the troop.
伯纳黛特想要
Bernadette's urge to
躲避  发怒  或是用排泄物扔普丽娅的冲动
shun, scowl or fling her waste at Priya
是与生俱来的
is hard-wired into her DNA.
我没有扔自己排泄物的冲动
I don't have an urge to fling my waste.
相信我  你有的  每个人都有
Believe me, it's there, we all have it.
再给我来点酒我就示范给你看
Hit me with some more booze, and I'll show you.
好了  我们到了  这就是进行
All right, here we are -- this is the tavern
所有黑市武器交易的小酒馆
where all the black-market weapon trades go down.
我觉得我的角色不应该来这种地方
I don't think my character should be in a place like this.
大家都盯着她开始意淫
Everyone's undressing her with their eyes.
要是你不老是把剑掉到地上
Maybe if you stop dropping your sword
然后再弯腰去捡的话  也许就不会这样了
and bending over to pick it up.
好吧  我们到底要找什么
Okay, what exactly are we looking for?
一个叫"忧郁"的红发巨魔
Redheaded troll, goes by the name of Glumly.
据留言板上的消息说
According to the message boards,
如果你想在深更半夜
if you want to move stolen goods
转移偷来的东西的话  找他就对了
and it's after school hours, he's your guy.
莱纳德  你还要弄很久吗
Leonard, is this going to take much longer?
你不是说要过二人世界嘛
I thought we were going to spend some time together.
我在陪你呀  而且你也可以
Uh, we are. In the meantime,
建个新人物然后跟我们一块玩呀
you're welcome to whip up a quick character and join us.
你说笑呢
Seriously?
好吧  你得先输入信用卡号码
Well, you have to put in a credit card number,
不过真挺好玩的
but it's fun.
也许我该回家了
Maybe I should just go home.
巨魔来了  我跟上去了
Our troll just walked in! I got him!
我们找到他了  就快搞掂了
We got him. We're almost done.
那么你们打算怎么办
So, how do you guys want to play this?
狠狠教训他  你跟他说
Be ruthless. You tell him
如果他不从实招来的话  我们就
if he doesn't start talking, we'll register a complaint
向他的网络供应商做出正式投诉
with his Internet service provider.
谢尔顿  要是他是从有线电视公司
Sheldon,what if he gets his Internet
连接互联网的怎么办
from his cable company?
他会失去他的HBO有线电视
He could lose his HBO
和所有好看的原创电视节目
and all their delightful original programming.
我不管  我丢东西了  伙计
I don't care! I'm losin' it, man!
我们不如玩得聪明点
Why don't we play this smart?
试试"好妖精 坏妖精"
Try a little "good goblin, bad goblin."
神啊
Oh, dear Lord.
不  我觉得我们得更狡猾些
Nah, I think we have to be more subtle.
好了  我知道你们的意思了
Okay, I see where this is going.
好吧  我会跟他做爱
Fine, I'll have sex with him.
我们不是那个意思
That's not where it was going.
太好了  因为我很讨厌那样
Good, because I would hate that.
莱纳德  你这么忙  我们明天再说吧
Leonard, you're busy-- let's talk tomorrow.
等等  再等一会  你不高兴了吗
Oh, wait. Hang on. Are you upset?
不不  我觉得跟一个男人身男孩心的人约会很性感
No, no, I think it's sexy to date a boy trapped in a man's body.
太好了
Good, good.
我会告诉你进展的
I'll tell you what happens.
大家都还觉得我听不出讽刺呢
And people think I don't get sarcasm.
哇  哇  哇
Well, well, well.
看我们碰上谁了
Look who it is.
好的  友好些
Okay, be nice.
你好
Hello.
嗨  我们刚准备出去喝一杯
Hi. We're just heading out for a drink.
因为我现在会喝酒了
Because I do that now.
知足吧
Count your blessings
你不是只坦桑尼亚猩猩
you're not a Tanzanian chimp.
什么
What?
别听她的
Don't listen to her--
她冰激凌吃多了
she's had a lot of ice cream.
你想一起来吗
Do you want to join us?
谢谢  但是我得工作
Oh, thank you, but I have work to do.
四个女人走下楼
Four women walk down the stairs--
几个人能到大厅
how many reach the lobby?
你昨晚回家时  你妹妹说什么了吗
Did your sister say anything when you got home last night?
不要  别把我扯进来
Oh, no, don't put me in the middle of this.
我可不当你的中间人
I'm not going to be your go-between.
拜托  帮帮我
Come on, help me out.
我有麻烦吗
Am I in trouble?
不需要担心
There's no reason to worry.
我放心多了
That's a relief.
我肯定很多在幸福关系中的女人
I'm sure many women
会跟她们的前男友"山鸡"
in happy relationships spend their nights
视频聊天来度过漫漫长夜
Skyping with their ex-boyfriend Sanjay.
好消息  同志们  我找到那个黑客了
Good news, gentlemen-- I found our hacker.
什么  真的
What? Really?
对  没人能逃得出我的手掌心
Yeah. No one can hide from me,
瓦尔多不行  卡门圣迭戈不行
not Waldo, not Carmen San Diego,
娜塔莉·波特曼的裸照也不行
not even topless Natalie Portman.
我以前从没说过这话
I've never said these words before,
干得不错  霍华德
but good job, Howard!
谢谢  我们的罪犯是托德·札内基
Thanks. Our culprit is one Mr. Todd Zarnecki,
加利福尼亚州
2711 Ocean View Road,
卡尔斯拜德  海景路2711号
Carlsbad, California.
这名字和地址都渗着邪恶的气息
The name and the address drip with evil.
我们还知道什么
What else do we know about him?
还有很多  其实
Why, quite a bit, actually.
我打赌他是一个跟父母一起住的失败者
I'll bet he's some loser who lives with his parents.
对  他确实跟父母一起住
Yes, he does live with his parents.
这是他们家的谷歌地图照片
Here's a Google Earth shot of their house.
太好了  在死胡同里
Excellent! It's in a cul-de-sac.
我们可以把他包饺子
We can box him in.
等等  你要去那儿吗
Hold on, you're thinking of going there?
卡尔斯拜德离这只有几小时车程
Carlsbad is only a couple of hours away.
好吧
Fine.
你走到门口  敲门
You walk up to the house, knock on the door
然后要你的东西  他要是拒绝怎么办
and demand your stuff back. What if he says no?
我不知道你最近看没看新闻  莱纳德
I don't know if you've been following the news, Leonard,
最近在拷问领域有很多
but there have been some terrific advancements
很棒的进展
in the field of torture.
没人要被拷问
No one's getting tortured.
好吧  我们会遵守日内瓦公约
Fine, we'll abide by the Geneva Convention.
但是  问问你自己
But ask yourself this:
我们的一生中
in the course of our lives,
多少午饭钱被人抢走了
how much lunch money has been taken from us?
多少风筝
How many kites?
多少史酷比活页夹
How many Scooby-Doo Trapper Keepers?
我真的有那么一个夹子
I totally had one of those.
当然了
Of course you did.
那是整理学校作业最有趣又实用的工具
It was a fun and practical way of organizing your school work.
但是那些恶霸从我们手里抢走了它
But the bullies took it from us.
再也不会了
Well, no more.
今晚  我们要重拾尊严
Tonight, we take back our dignity,
我们与生俱来的权利和自尊
our birthright and our pride.
怎么样
What do you say?
谁跟我一起
Who's with me?
5点我有节hip-hop健身操课  我们能结束后走吗
I have a hip-hop aerobics class at 5:00; could we go after?
当然
Sure.
还有  今晚是安息日
Also, tonight's the Sabbath
我妈和我的传统是
and my mother and I have a tradition of
点亮蜡烛  一起看《幸运之轮》
lighting the candles and watching Wheel of Fortune, so...
如果我们我们8点出发
If we could leave at 8:00,
我们还能在10点
we'd still be able to
最晚10:30重获我们的权利
regain our birthright at 10:00, 10:30 latest.
行
Fine.
莱纳德
Leonard?
完了  我不知道能不能连续两晚
Oh, geez, I-I don't know if I can ditch Priya
都放普丽娅鸽子
two nights in a row.
拜托  伙计
Oh, come on, man.
男人如手足  女人如衣服
Bros before...
我妹亦然
...my sister.
不管了
Aw, screw it.
-我去  -我也去
- I'm in. - Me, too.
还有我
And me.
稍等
One moment.
为了抓住网络罪犯  我会不顾一切
I'm hell-bent on catching a cyber criminal,
至于流行性病毒感冒  还是算了吧
not the common cold.
抱歉  我以为有事耽搁是因为
I'm sorry, I thought this delay was
你要和你妈妈一起看《幸运之轮》
so you could watch Wheel of Fortune with your mother.
确实如此
I am.
她正在漂胡子呢
She's just bleaching her mustache.
不信你听
Check it out.
妈  "给两头猜中间"游戏时间
Hey, Ma! "Before and After!"
4个词  17个字母  有两个N  一个V
Four words, 17 letters, two N's, one V!
"狼的腰包"
"Fanny pack of wolves!"
太厉害了
That's incredible.
对啊  她差不多算是这个节目的专家
Yeah, she's kind of a Wheel savant.
啊哦  普丽娅打来了
Uh-oh, that's Priya.
你用西塔琴作为她的铃声可不好哦  兄弟
Sitar music for her ringtone is not cool, dude.
小点声
Hit the...
宝贝
Hey, sweetie.
真的很抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry.
我今天要工作到很晚
I'm gonna be working late.
对  我也想你
Yeah, I-I miss you, too.
没问题  等我到家了我会打给你的
Okay, sure, I'll call you when I get home.
好的  拜
Okay, bye-bye.
干得好
Very nice.
你欺骗了我的妹妹
You lie to my sister.
那算他对你妹妹做过的最好的事情了
That's the nicest thing he does to your sister.
猜猜是谁
Oh, guess who.
掩护我
Cover for me.
普丽娅  怎么了
Hello, Priya. What's up?
我怎么会知道莱纳德是不是在工作
How would I know if Leonard's at work or not?
你疑心病不要太重啦
Don't be suspicious.
听着  如果你想继续你和莱纳德的恋情
Look, if you want your relationship with Leonard
无论是让你怒目而视的
to continue, you're going to have to believe
或是荒谬可笑的借口
whatever wild-eyed, cockamamie excuse
你都得信任这白恶魔所说的
the white devil has the nerve to offer you.
懂了吗  好的  再见
Okay? Yeah, bye-bye.
你欠我个人情
You owe me.
新猜谜  妈
New puzzle, Ma!
"同姓不同名"
"Same name"!
一个N  两个D  三个0
One N, two D's, three O's!
乌比·戈德堡和鲁布·戈德堡
Whoopi and Rube Goldberg!
真是太不可思议了
That's uncanny.
我知道  这就是她的超能力
I know. It's her superpower.
错  还包括她会颤抖的臂脂肪区
Well, that and jiggling her arm fat.
真不敢相信我们为了与那个家伙当面对峙
I can't believe we're going all the way to San Diego
居然一路杀到圣地亚哥
to confront this guy.
就是  我们就像坏蛋  对不
Yeah, we're kind of bad-asses, aren't we?
十足的坏
Totally.
我们在这过夜
Hey, how about we stay the night
然后一早去乐高积木乐园  怎么样
and hit Legoland in the morning?
海洋世界更好玩
Sea World is better.
那里有虎鲸明星莎木  绝对给你带来重量级的乐趣
It has Shamu, who is literally tons of fun.
不过目前  咱们还是把注意力集中在托德·札内基身上
But for the moment, let's stay focused on Todd Zarnecki.
就是  托德·札内基  我们来抓你啦
Yeah, we're coming for you, Todd Zarnecki.
我郑重声明一下  乐高积木乐园有更多互动
And for the record, Legoland is more interactive.
我几乎为那个傻坐在错层的
I almost feel sorry for the poor fool,
郊区农场的可怜虫感到抱歉
sitting in his split-level suburban ranch,
完全没意识到有一群复仇的人们
unaware that a vengeful horde
正以每小时71迈的速度
is barreling down the San Diego Freeway
飞驰在圣地亚哥的高速上
at 71 miles an hour.
开慢点  快车手
Ease up there, lead foot.
你想车毁人亡呀
You trying to get us killed?
恕我冒昧  我们先用这张
I took the liberty of burning us
英雄出征任务的混音CD热热身吧
a mix of heroic questing music.
上面写的是"碧昂斯秀色可餐舞蹈混音专辑"
This says "Beyonce Bootylicious Dance Mix."
这是张可重写CD
It's a re-writable CD.
别废话  快放进去
Just put it in.
碧昂斯  坑爹呢
Beyonce? Really?
她曲线动人  而且她身材是好
She's curvy and she owns it.
我喜欢这点
I like that.
没错  我感受到那份激情了
Oh, yeah, I'm feeling it.
我们的愤怒张开双翅
We are winged fury!
即便这样  还是没有任何理由
Which is still no excuse
超过高速公布的速度限制标准
for going over the posted speed limit.
下次我们去教训某人的时候
Next time we go to kick someone's ass,
坐火车去得了
we take the train.
火车总是我的第一选择
I always prefer the train.
谢尔顿  走吧
Sheldon, let's go.
来了
Coming.
你为什么要带上这个
Why did you bring that?
没有什么武器能比克林贡的荣誉剑
No weapon strikes more fear into a man's heart
更能把恐惧扎进一个人的心
than a Klingon bat'leth.
好吧  我们先把话说清楚
Okay, let's get clear on something.
我们来这是为了告诉那个家伙把你的东西
We're just going to tell this guy to transfer all of
全部转回你的账户上  然后我们就回家
your stuff back into your account and then be on our way.
没人要用荣誉剑扎任何人
No one's bat'lething anybody.
所以我锋利的刀刃今晚是尝不到鲜血咯
So my blade shall not taste blood tonight?
对
No.
好吧  现在我觉得举着这东西很傻逼
Well, now I just feel silly holding it.
来吧
Come on.
那我至少能一脚踹开他家门吧
Can I at least kick down the door?
随便踹  但某天
You're welcome to try, but the other day,
你打开个联邦快递的盒子都花了十五分钟
it took you 15 minutes to get into a FedEx box.
谁呀
Who is it?
你的末日
Your doom!
别说"你的末日"
Don't say "your doom."
谁会给自己的末日开门
Who opens the door for their doom?
说得有道理
Good point.
一篮小狗狗
Basket of puppies.
有事吗
What?
呃
Uh...
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
你是托德·札内基吗
Are you Todd Zarnecki?
是  你是谁
Yeah. Who are you?
我是艾泽拉斯的谢耳朵
I am Sheldor of Azeroth.
我要你把我的东西还回来
I want my things back.
我可不这么认为
I don't think so.
给我看看
Let me see that.
小心点  那可是珍藏品
Careful. That's a collectible.
我知道
I know.
我一直很想要一个
I've always wanted one.
他比我们想象的还要狡猾
Well, he's even more cunning than we thought.
知道吗  闹笑话的是他
You know, the joke's on him.
没有真品凭证
Without the certificate of authenticity,
那把荣誉剑分文不值
that bat'leth is worthless.
对  他正中下怀  进了咱们的圈套
Yeah, he walked right into our trap.
乐高积木公园如今成了遥不可及的梦了
Legoland seems like a hollow dream now.
完了
Uh-oh.
-怎么了  -出事了
- What's the matter? - Something's wrong.
车不吃油了
I'm not getting any gas.
有人知道内燃机吗
Anybody know anything about internal combustion engines?
当然
Of course.
-19世纪的老科技   -非常基本的常识
- 19th-century technology. - Very basic.
有人懂怎么修理内燃机吗
Does anybody know how to fix an internal combustion engine?
-不懂  -不懂  -完全不懂
- No. - No. - Not a clue.
那最好打电话让人来接咱们
Well, we'd better call somebody to come pick us up.
如果那人有辆火车的话  那真是一级棒
It'd be swell if they had a train.
谢谢你  佩妮
Thank you, Penny.
不客气
No problem.
对了  莱纳德
So, Leonard,
你没有让你女朋友来接你
I think it's interesting you didn't call your girlfriend
这事有点儿意思
to come get you.
我告诉她我在工作
Uh, I kind of told her I was working.
所以你对她撒谎了
So you lied to her.
真有意思
Also interesting.
对  她不是很懂
Yeah, she doesn't really understand
魔兽争霸的整个冒险角色扮演游戏
the whole Warcraft adventure-role-playing thing.
她不懂没关系  只要她漂亮就好了嘛
Well, doesn't matter if she gets it, as long as she's pretty.
这事儿才有意思呢  莱纳德
This one's funny, Leonard.
你怎么会跟这么懂事的女孩分手呢
How come you couldn't make it work with her?
那你们至少把谢尔顿那些假玩意儿要回来了吧
So did you at least get Sheldon's fake stuff back?
没有  我们伟大的寻物征途失败了
No. We failed in our noble quest.
怎么回事
How come?
托德·札内基是个贱人
Todd Zarnecki was mean.
好了  坐稳了
All right. Hang on.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
我要让你们见识下  在内布拉斯加是怎么完成寻物征途的
I'm gonna show you how we finish a quest in Nebraska.
哇  碧昂斯
Oh. Beyonce.
这可不是碧昂斯
This ain't no Beyonce.
又怎么了
Now what?
把我朋友的东西还回来
Give my friend his stuff back.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
好吧  告诉你个好消息
Well, then, good news.
今天你那个私密的小地方
Today's the day a girl's finally going to touch you
终于有女人光临了
in your little special place.
现在把他的东西还给他
Now give him his stuff back.
好好
Okay.
我们做到了
We did it!
我都说了是"我们"
I said, "we."
让门开着
Oh, hold the door.
-哦  你好  -你好
- Oh, hi. - Hi.
来看莱纳德吗
Going to see Leonard?
对
Yes.
你近来如何
How have you been?
很好  你呢
Fine. You?
非常好  谢谢
Very well, thank you.
终于到了  很高兴见到你
All right, well, great seeing you.
我也是
Yeah. You, too.
艾米说得对
Amy's right.
我真想拿屎甩她
I do want to fling my poop at her.